INDRAJEET VADAR

Sanjay Park, Vimannagar, Pune



indrajeet.vadar04@outlook.com





linkedin.com/in/indrajeet-vadar-113a6a32

Summary

Agricultural Engineer with Experience in manufacturing of Farm Machinery. Working and various operations In Agriculture. Having experience in customer service and Logistics operations In E- Commerce Field. With Successful Completion Of PRO/E Wildfire 5.0 Course of 2 months.

Experience



Operations Associate(Pune, MH)

Xpressbees (BusyBees Logistics Solutions Pvt. Ltd.)

Nov 2015 - Aug 2016 (10 months)

- Worked as Operations Associate(B2B) in the company.
- With handling pick up operations of all the shipment of the major E commerce companies--Paytm, Snapdeal, Shopclues, Voonik, Tolexo.
- Made sure all the shipment are picked from the Merchant warehouse on the same day so they could be connected further in transit by fulfillment team.
- · Maintenance of daily MIS file of all the shipments in EXCEL and give detailed Information of the Shipments in tabular format giving the Servile level of the Pickup. Upload daily the Shipment file in ,csv Format in the system so it could be accessed PAN India and the so operations could go smoothly.
- Maintain constant contact with the HUB and the Ground employees for update on the operations



Junior Engineer

iEnergizer ITES Pvt. Ltd., Noida(UP)

Dec 2014 - Jun 2015 (7 months)

- Worked as Customer service Executive(Junior Engineer--technical support) In Samsung Process.
- · Process of Hand Held devices of Samsung
- Handle 80 to 100 inbound calls including General Queries and Technical Queries.
- Understand the details of the Issues of the customer and resolve the issues on same call.
- Maintain the data of the customer in the software GCIC of Samsung.
- Achieve daily target of TAT and ensure the service level is maintained.
- Remotely access the customers Mobile using the Samsung Smart Tutor App and resolved the software issue on call.



Summer Trainee:

JYOTIRLING AGRO PRIVATE LIMITED

Mar 2012 - Apr 2012 (2 months)

Was Given In Plant training on various parts, Manufacturing of Reversible Mouldboard plough and also manufacturing of Tractor drawn trailer. Involved in manufacturing of Farm machinery



Summer Trainee:

MITCON Consultancy and Engineering Services Ltd.

Jan 2012 - Feb 2012 (2 months)

PRO/ENGINEER WILDFIRE 5.0-- creating a new part, an assembly, or drawing, using a set of Pro/E commands, practiced the process systematically and made parametric designs. Created individual parts, assemblies, and drawings of various machine parts.



Summer Trainee:

National Dairy Research Institute

May 2011 - May 2011 (1 month)

Hands On Training on processing, manufacturing of dairy products.

Study of Layout and operations of Dairy plant. Manufacturing of Various dairy products. Farm stead Planning and layout.



Summer Trainee:

Northern Region Farm Machinery Training and Testing Institute

May 2010 - May 2010 (1 month)

Hands On Training in Operation, Repair and maintenance of Tractor and Farm implements. Detailed study of Various Farm machinery and Tractor

Education:



Mahatma Phule Krishi Vidyapeeth

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Agricultural Engineering

Department of specialization in Final year of B.Tech-Farm machinery and power



The New College, Kolhapur

Junior College, Science

2006 - 2008



Venkateshwara English School, Ichalkaranji

1993 - 2006

Skills:

Microsoft Office • Team Management • Research • Business-to-Business (B2B) • Logistics Management • Leadership • Microsoft PowerPoint • Management • Microsoft Excel • Customer Service.Pro/E wildfire 5.0

Languages:

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi